Department of Geography fonds
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
- Course outlines and exams, 1965 - 1987; F-12-6; 1.55 m of textual records
  - GEOG 265 British Columbia; Spring and Fall (EV DT) '84; Spring, Fall (EV) '85, 1984 - 1985; F-12-6-0-0-297 (Archival box - standard 12-30)
  - GEOG 301 Geographic Ideas and Methodology; Spring, Summer and Fall, 1984; F-12-6-0-0-298 (Archival box - standard 12-30)
  - GEOG 314 Climatology I; Fall, 1984; F-12-6-0-0-299 (Archival box - standard 12-30)
  - GEOG 319 Physical Interactions in the Environment; Spring '84; Spring (CS) '86, 1984 - 1986; F-12-6-0-0-300 (Archival box - standard 12-30)
  - GEOG 346 Geography of Contemporary Industrial Societies; Spring and Summer '84; Summer and Fall '85; Spring (DT) and Fall '86, 1984 - 1986; F-12-6-0-0-301 (Archival box - standard 12-30)
  - GEOG 353 Aerial Photographic Interpretation; Spring 'and Fall '84, Fall '85, 1984 - 1985; F-12-6-0-0-302 (Archival box - standard 12-30)
  - GEOG 361 Introduction to Urban Geography; Fall, 1984 - 1987; F-12-6-0-0-303 (Archival box - standard 12-30)
  - GEOG 383 Regional Planning I; Fall '84-'85; Spring '85-'86, Fall (EV) '86-'87, 1984 - 1987; F-12-6-0-0-304 (Archival box - standard 12-30)
  - GEOG 411 Models in Hydrometeorology; Spring, 1984 - 1986; F-12-6-0-0-305 (Archival box - standard 12-30)
  - GEOG 414-5 Applied Climatology; Spring '84-'85, '87; Fall '87, 1984 - 1987; F-12-6-0-0-306 (Archival box - standard 12-30)
  - GEOG 415 Biogeography; Spring, 1984 - 1986; F-12-6-0-0-307 (Archival box - standard 12-30)
  - GEOG 416 Pleistocene Geography; Fall, 1984 - 1986; F-12-6-0-0-308 (Archival box - standard 12-30)
  - GEOG 426 Industrial Organization, Location and Planning; Spring '84-'86; Fall '87, 1984 - 1987; F-12-6-0-0-309 (Archival box - standard 12-30)
  - GEOG 431 Landscape in Science, Art, Music and Literature; Fall '84, Spring '87, 1984 - 1987; F-12-6-0-0-310 (Archival box - standard 12-30)
  - GEOG 444 Regional Planning II; Fall (EV) '84; Spring '87, 1984 - 1987; F-12-6-0-0-311 (Archival box - standard 12-30)
  - GEOG 453 Remote Sensing; Spring [also see GEOG 419], 1984 - 1987; F-12-6-0-0-312 (Archival box - standard 12-30)
  - GEOG 111 Physical Geography; Summer (regular and SS), 1985; F-12-6-0-0-313 (Archival box - standard 12-31)
  - GEOG 111 Physical Geography; Spring, Fall (regular and EV), 1985; F-12-6-0-0-314 (Archival box - standard 12-31)
  - GEOG 121 Economic Geography; Spring, Summer, Fall (regular and DT), 1985; F-12-6-0-0-315 (Archival box - standard 12-31)
  - GEOG 250 Cartography I; Spring, Fall, 1985; F-12-6-0-0-316 (Archival box - standard 12-31)
  - GEOG 262 Canada; Spring (DC), Sumemr, Fall, 1985; F-12-6-0-0-317 (Archival box - standard 12-31)
  - GEOG 312 Geography of Natural Hazards; Fall (EV and DT) '85, '87; Spring, Summer, Fall '86, 1985 - 1987; F-12-6-0-0-318 (Archival box - standard 12-31)
  - GEOG 313 Geomorphology; Spring, Summer '85; Summer, Fall '86, 1985 - 1986; F-12-6-0-0-319 (Archival box - standard 12-31)
  - GEOG 314 Climatology I; Fall, 1985; F-12-6-0-0-320 (Archival box - standard 12-31)
  - GEOG 315 Biogeography I; Fall, 1985 - 1987; F-12-6-0-0-321 (Archival box - standard 12-31)
  - GEOG 317 Soil Geography; Spring and Summer (CS) '85, Summer and Fall (CS) '86; Spring, Fall '87, 1985 - 1987; F-12-6-0-0-322 (Archival box - standard 12-31)
  - GEOG 322 Geography of Primary Activities; Spring '85-'86; Fall '86, 1985 - 1986; F-12-6-0-0-323 (Archival box - standard 12-31)
  - GEOG 323 Geography of Manufacturing; Fall, 1985 - 1986; F-12-6-0-0-324 (Archival box - standard 12-31)
  - GEOG 324 Geography of Transportation; Spring and Summer, (CS); Spring and Fall, 1985 - 1986; F-12-6-0-0-325 (Archival box - standard 12-31)
  - GEOG 325 Geography of Tertiary and Quartenary Activities; Summer '85; Spring, Fall '86, '87, 1985 - 1987; F-12-6-0-0-326 (Archival box - standard 12-31)
  - GEOG 343 Geography of Transitional Societies; Spring, Fall '85; Spring '87, 1985 - 1987; F-12-6-0-0-327 (Archival box - standard 12-32)
  - GEOG 344 Geography of Modern Industrial Societies; Fall '85, Summer '86-'87, 1985 - 1987; F-12-6-0-0-328 (Archival box - standard 12-32)
  - GEOG 369 Human Microgeography; Spring '85, Fall '86, 1985 - 1986; F-12-6-0-0-329 (Archival box - standard 12-32)
  - GEOG 375 Historical Geography; Fall '85, Spring (EV) '86; Summer (EV) '87, 1985 - 1987; F-12-6-0-0-330 (Archival box - standard 12-32)
  - GEOG 382 Population Geography; Spring '85, Fall '86-'87, 1985 - 1987; F-12-6-0-0-331 (Archival box - standard 12-32)
  - GEOG 423 Geogpahy of Tourism and Outdoor Recreation; Fall '85, Spring '86, 1985 - 1986; F-12-6-0-0-332 (Archival box - standard 12-32)
  - GEOG 460 Selected Regions (Western Europe); Fall, 1985; F-12-6-0-0-333 (Archival box - standard 12-32)
  - GEOG 101 General Geography; Spring, Summer, 1986; F-12-6-0-0-334 (Archival box - standard 12-32)
  - GEOG 111 Physical Geography; Spring, Summer (regular and SS), 1986; F-12-6-0-0-335 (Archival box - standard 12-32)
  - GEOG 111 Physical Geography; Fall (regular and EV), 1986; F-12-6-0-0-336 (Archival box - standard 12-32)
  - GEOG 112 Introductory Geology; Spring, Summer, Fall, 1986; F-12-6-0-0-337 (Archival box - standard 12-32)
  - GEOG 121 Economic Geography; Spring (regular and EV), Summer, Fall, 1986; F-12-6-0-0-338 (Archival box - standard 12-32)
  - GEOG 141 Social Geography; Spring (regular and EV), Summer, Fall, 1986; F-12-6-0-0-339 (Archival box - standard 12-32)
  - GEOG 250 Cartography I; Spring and Fall (EV), Summer '86-'87, 1986 - 1987; F-12-6-0-0-340 (Archival box - standard 12-32)
  - GEOG 262 Canada; Spring (regular and DT), Summer, Fall, 1986; F-12-6-0-0-341 (Archival box - standard 12-32)
  - GEOG 263 Selected Regions (Africa); Summer, Fall '86-'87, 1986 - 1987; F-12-6-0-0-342 (Archival box - standard 12-32)
  - GEOG 265 British Columbia; Spring '86-'87, Fall '87, 1986 - 1987; F-12-6-0-0-343 (Archival box - standard 12-32)
  - GEOG 301 Geographic Ideas and Methodology; Spring, Summer, Fall, 1986 - 1987; F-12-6-0-0-344 (Archival box - standard 12-33)
  - GEOG 314 Climatology I; Fall, 1986; F-12-6-0-0-345 (Archival box - standard 12-33)
  - GEOG 315 Biogeography I; Fall '86 and '87, 1986 - 1987; F-12-6-0-0-346 (Archival box - standard 12-33)
  - GEOG 351 Cartography II; Spring, Fall '86; Summer, Fall '87, 1986 - 1987; F-12-6-0-0-347 (Archival box - standard 12-33)
  - GEOG 353 Aerial Photographic Interpretation; Spring and Fall '86; Fall '87, 1986 - 1987; F-12-6-0-0-348 (Archival box - standard 12-33)
  - GEOG 412 Quarternary Geology and Geomorphology; Spring, Fall, 1986; F-12-6-0-0-349 (Archival box - standard 12-33)
  - GEOG 101 General Geography; Spring, Fall, 1987; F-12-6-0-0-350 (Archival box - standard 12-33)
  - GEOG 111 Physical Geography; Spring, 1987; F-12-6-0-0-351 (Archival box - standard 12-33)
  - GEOG 111 Physical Geography; Fall (regular, EV, SEN), 1987; F-12-6-0-0-352 (Archival box - standard 12-33)
  - GEOG 112 Introductory Geology; Spring, Fall, 1987; F-12-6-0-0-353 (Archival box - standard 12-33)
  - GEOG 121 Economic Geography; Spring, Summer, Fall, 1987; F-12-6-0-0-354 (Archival box - standard 12-33)
  - GEOG 141 Social / Cultural Geography; Spring (regular, EV, and DT), Summer, Fall (regular, EV, and Matsqui), 1987; F-12-6-0-0-355 (Archival box - standard 12-33)
  - GEOG 262 Canada; Spring (regular and EV), Summer (regular and EV DT), Fall, 1987; F-12-6-0-0-356 (Archival box - standard 12-33)
  - GEOG 313 Geomorphology; Spring and Fall, 1987; F-12-6-0-0-357 (Archival box - standard 12-33)
  - GEOG 314 Climatology I; Summer, 1987; F-12-6-0-0-358 (Archival box - standard 12-33)
  - GEOG 346DC Geography of Contemporary Industrial Societies; Fall (regular and EV), 1987; F-12-6-0-0-359 (Archival box - standard 12-33)
- Publications, 1972 - 1985; F-12-7; 8 cm of textual records
  Series consists of departmental publications, including course offerings booklets.
  - Careers in geography, 1982 - 1984; F-12-7-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 12-22)
  - Course offerings, 1972 - 1975; F-12-7-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 12-22)
  - Graduate studies in geography, F-12-7-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 12-22)
  - Miscellaneous, 1980 - 1985; F-12-7-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 12-22)
  - Discussion papers #2 (1978): The Distribution of Dree Sponsored Manufacturing Investments in Atlantic Canada, 1972 - 1975; F-12-7-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 12-22)
  - Discussion papers #8: Natural Science Studies of Burnaby and Belcarra Mountains, F-12-7-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 12-22)
  - Discussion papers #16: Ethnic Vancouver: Essays in Cultural Geography, F-12-7-0-0-7 (Archival box - standard 12-22)
  - Discussion papers #20: the university goes to town, 1977 - 1984; F-12-7-0-0-8 (Archival box - standard 12-22)